http://www.cinnzeo.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
About This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information that is collected, used, and shared when you visit https://cinnzeo.com/
This includes our mobile sites and any associated websites of Cinnaroll Bakeries Limited.
This policy does not apply to information we might collect from you offline.
Your use of this website indicates you agree to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Effective Date: November 5, 2019
Drafted by: Not A Lawyer
Reviewed & Approved by:
Who we are
We are Cinnzeo ™ Bakery Cafe, a division of Cinnaroll Bakeries Limited.
Contact Information
Cinnzeo ™ Bakery Cafe2140 Pegasus Rd N.E.Calgary, Alberta, Canada T2E 8G8https://cinnzeo.com/
Tel: +1 (403) 255-4556Fax: +1 (403) 259-5124Email: info@cinnzeo.com
What Personal Data we collect & why we collect it
When you visit this site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the site, and information about how you interact with the site.
Comments
Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of Cinnzeo.com. Depending on the settings, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the personal data provided by the user, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments. If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Service
Privacy Policy
Description
Gravatar (Automattic Inc.)
Privacy Policy.
Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows Gravityforms.com and Gravityhelp.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter’s email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar – even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.
Personal Data collected: email address and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
SPAM protection
This type of service analyzes the traffic of cinnzeo.com, potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.
Service
Privacy Policy
Description
Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)
Privacy Policy
Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google privacy policy and terms of use.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Shield participant.
Akismet (Automattic Inc.)
Privacy Policy
Akismet is a SPAM protection service provided by Automattic Inc.
Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Place of processing: United States
Cookies
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our clients use the site–you can read more about how Google uses your personal information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the site.
Service
Privacy Policy
Description
Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Gravityforms.com and Gravityhelp.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Shield participant.
HubSpot Analytics
Privacy Policy – Opt Out
HubSpot Analytics is an analytics service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States .
Tag Management
This type of service helps manage tags and scripts on cinnzeo.com in a centralized fashion. This results in the User’s Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this data.
Service
Privacy Policy
Description
Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)
Privacy Policy
Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Shield participant.
Who we share your data with
We may share your data with third parties for advertising & marketing purposes or to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
When you subscribe to a service or newsletter, we will maintain your information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
What rights you have over your data
The rights of Users
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.
In particular, Users have the right to do the following:
Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.
Details about the right to object to processing
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.
Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.
How to exercise these rights
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
What third parties we receive data from
Displaying content from external platforms
This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of cinnzeo.com and interact with them. This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
Service
Privacy Policy
Description
Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
Privacy Policy
Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows Gravityforms.com and Gravityhelp.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Shield participant.
Typekit (Adobe Systems Incorporated)
Privacy Policy.
Typekit is a typeface visualization service provided by Adobe Systems Incorporated that allows Gravityforms.com and Gravityhelp.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Shield participant.
Gravatar (Automattic Inc.)
Privacy Policy.
Gravatar is an image visualization service provided by Automattic Inc. that allows Gravityforms.com and Gravityhelp.com to incorporate content of this kind on its pages. Please note that if Gravatar images are used for comment forms, the commenter’s email address or parts of it may be sent to Gravatar – even if the commenter has not signed up for that service.
Personal Data collected: email address and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States
How we treat “Do Not Track” requests
Please not that we do not alter our data collection and use practices when we see a “Do Not Track” signal from your browser.
GDPR regulatory disclosure requirements
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information listed.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you, or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States of America.
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Additional Information
Information not contained in this policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
Privacy Policy
HANDCRAFTED BY BLKWTR CREATIVE © 2019
